const quizData = [
	{
		question: "What is the past form of 'eat'?",
		answers: {
			a: "eat",
			b: "ate",
			c: "eaten",
			d: "have ate",
		},
		correctAnswer: "b",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is present continuous tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I am eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "b",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is present perfect tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I am eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "c",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is present perfect continuous tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I am eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "d",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is past continuous tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I was eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "b",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is past perfect tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I was eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "c",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is past perfect continuous tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I was eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "d",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is future continuous tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I will be eating rice",
			c: "I have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "b",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is future perfect tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I will be eating rice",
			c: "I will have eaten rice",
			d: "I have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "c",
	},
	{
		question: "Which sentence is future perfect continuous tense?",
		answers: {
			a: "I eat rice",
			b: "I will be eating rice",
			c: "I will have eaten rice",
			d: "I will have been eating rice for 1 year",
		},
		correctAnswer: "d",
	},
];
